<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Author on ii.nz</title>
    <link>https://ii.nz/author/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Author on ii.nz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ii.nz/author/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/zach-mandeville/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/zach-mandeville/</guid>
      <description>Zach is a software engineer at ii. He loves sharing the excitement and awesome potential of technology through his work, storytelling, and mad science projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/caleb-woodbine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/caleb-woodbine/</guid>
      <description>Caleb is a software engineer at ii. Driven by community, he loves the collaboration of individuals - especially through Open Source. Caleb contributes to the Kubernetes Infrastructure working group, sig-testing, and the conformance working group. Caleb also spends way too much time with container technologies and Golang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/stephen-heywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/stephen-heywood/</guid>
      <description>Stephen Heywood is a cloud-native advocate that brings together 20 years of exploring open source technologies with an extensive set of skills from various industries.
From tertiary education (12 years); corporate IT (5 years) and the electricity sector (8 years), each has provided him with a wealth of information and a long history of industry certifications.
To unwind, Stephen enjoys an eclectic range of hobbies, from architecture, podcasts, movies while learning about different programming languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/riaan-kleinhans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/riaan-kleinhans/</guid>
      <description>Riaan Kleinhans is the Project manager at ii. Helping a team of talented people to focus on what they do best. Keeping the team organized and on target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Rynhard</title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/andrew-rynhard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/andrew-rynhard/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/hippie-hacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/hippie-hacker/</guid>
      <description>Chris McClimans is first and foremost a visionary. Chris envisions a world where everyone shares their knowledge base as well as their skills and resources. In our world of tech, this happens through open source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/berno-kleinhans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/berno-kleinhans/</guid>
      <description>The first member of the ii groupies club. Striving for impactful change in the world through relationships and opensource collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ii.nz/author/brenda-peel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ii.nz/author/brenda-peel/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to get in touch with ii, Brenda is your first point of contact.
At ii, Brenda Peel seamlessly manages and coordinates all things from start to finish. There is nothing too big for Brenda to conquer. And she does it all with a smile.
Before moving to New Zealand with her husband and two dogs, Brenda worked as a Publisher Relationship Manager and Digital Project Coordinator in Cape Town, South Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
